http://www.shop.bt.com/help/policies/our-security-policy

Media   >
Blank Media (CD, DVD & Blu-Ray)
Bundle Offers   >
Buy any two Portals and save £50!
Bundles
Whole Home WiFi Bundles
Prizes   >
Competitions
COVID-19: We're still delivering to customers from our online store. Get the latest updates here >
All Media
Blank Media (CD, DVD & Blu-Ray)
Processors
Other Drives (Optical, USB)
All Other Drives (Optical, USB)
Bundle Offers
Buy any two Portals and save £50!
Our security policy
We take very great care to ensure that any personal information you enter on the BT Shop website is kept safe. The following section explains how we keep your data secure.
Security Technology
When you type in your registration details or credit card number, our website automatically changes into secure mode. When you're submitting details to the BT Shop over the Internet, security is handled as follows:
Firstly, when your browser (e.g. Internet Explorer) connects with the secure side of our server (website computer), that connection is between you and the server alone.
Secondly, the information you're sending us will be encrypted before it begins its journey over the internet to BT.com. This ensures that it can't be read by anyone else while it's in transit. In other words, during the communications between your browser and our server, the information is scrambled. This is known as encryption, the grade of encryption used could be 128, 168 or 256 bits, depending on the browser. 128bit encryption uses billions (2 to power of 128) of possible combinations to scramble the information. The enabling technology is called Transport Layer Security, or TLS for short.
Thirdly, any information we store internally so we can process your order, is kept on a computer system that operates independently of the web server and doesn't use an operating system that is prone to viruses, hacking etc.
In summary, we've taken the appropriate measures to ensure that your personal information is not unlawfully processed. BT Shop uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. BT Shop treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorised access. However, no information transferred over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed to be completely secure.
Why does a screen prompt tell me my security certificate is out of date?
A certificate is a piece of software that your browser uses to encrypt your personal information when it's being transmitted to and from the BT Shop. The message you're getting is probably erroneous. It's usually caused by older browser versions that don't process date information correctly. The solution is easy. Upgrade your browser to a newer version.
Why can't I see a padlock icon in Internet Explorer but can in Netscape Navigator?
Some older versions of Internet Explorer do not use the padlock icon to indicate whether an online page is using a secure protocol. To check whether a page is secure, look at the URL in the Address window. If it starts with the letters https instead of the usual http, it is secure. Alternatively, right click your mouse over the Address window and select Properties. If the page is secure, you'll see the words Transfer Protocol Privacy protected.
Netscape Navigator shows a locked padlock to indicate when a page is using a secure protocol. However, a few pages on the BT Shop or on BT.com still use frames that are effectively pages within pages. When this is the case, a secure frame within a page that doesn't contain secure information will still show an unlocked padlock. This doesn't mean that your personal information is insecure. To check, look in the Location window. If the page starts with the letters https instead of the usual http, it is secure. Alternatively, move your mouse over the frame you want to check, right click and select Open in New Window. That frame will now be in a new window and should show a closed padlock.
What are cookies and does BT use them?
You can find details on what cookies are, how BT uses them and how to disable them in our Privacy Policy.
Information on cookies can be found in our Help section.
Call: Closed
Email:
shop@bt.com
We are open:
Monday to Friday 9am - 5pm
Here to help
New to BT Shop
Help guides
Learn more articles
BT disability services
Cookie preferences
Delivery & returns
Rearrange a delivery
Need to return something?
Delivery charges
Track a parcel
Shopping
Get Wi-Fi in every room with BT Whole Home Wi-Fi
Create the Smart Home of your dreams with BT Shop
Find the right products using our Smart Home Scenarios
Buying a baby monitor? See our ranges, reviews and guides
See our Latest Deals
Call: Closed
Email:
shop@bt.com
We are open:
Monday to Friday, 9am - 5pm
BT Shop is a trading style of British Telecommunications Public Limited Company, which is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority. British Telecommunications Public Limited Company is acting as a credit broker for PayPal Credit.
PayPal Credit is a trading name of PayPal (Europe) Sarl et Cie, SCA, 22-24 Boulevard Royal, L2449 Luxembourg. PayPal Credit is subject to status, terms and conditions apply.
Cookies
Terms and conditions
Privacy policy
About us
Security policy
Sitemap
Cookies on BT Shop
We use cookies to do things like remember what you've added to your shopping basket and show you content we think you'll be interested in.
If you're happy with the use of cookies by BT Shop and selected third parties, click OK to continue.
About cookies
OK
About cookies
Some cookies are essential - we can't provide our services without them.
Other cookies can be turned off, although our website won't work as well without them.
Click OK to accept cookies and continue.
Edit settings
OK
More about cookies
Functional cookies
These cookies let us do things like remember your login details and settings and provide support using live chat.
Allow functional cookies?
Yes
No
Allow all cookies
Targeting cookies
We use these cookies to do things like show you content and promotions we think
you'll like while you're browsing BT Shop and other sites. They also let you share pages with social media sites.
Allow targeting cookies?
Yes
No
Allow all cookies
Thanks, you're all set!
You can change your cookies settings whenever you like by using the 'Cookie preferences' link at the bottom of every page on this website.
OK
Your cookie settings
Here are your current cookie settings.
Necessary and performance cookies (required)
